import { Flashcard } from "../logic/types";


export const flashcards: Flashcard[] = [
    {
        id: 1,
        front: "der Tisch",
        back: "the table",
        hint: "Starts with T",
        tags: ["noun", "german", "furniture"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        front: "la silla",
        back: "the chair",
        hint: "Starts with S",
        tags: ["noun", "spanish", "furniture"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        front: "bonjour",
        back: "hello",
        tags: ["phrase", "french", "greeting"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        front: "arigato",
        back: "thank you",
        hint: "Expression of gratitude",
        tags: ["phrase", "japanese"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        front: "What is the capital of France?",
        back: "Paris",
        tags: ["geography", "europe"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        front: "What is H2O?",
        back: "Water",
        hint: "A common chemical compound",
        tags: ["science", "chemistry"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        front: "console.log()",
        back: "Outputs a message to the web console.",
        tags: ["programming", "javascript", "webdev"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        front: "React useState hook",
        back: "Lets you add state to functional components.",
        hint: "Returns a stateful value and a function to update it.",
        tags: ["programming", "javascript", "react"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        front: "len() in Python",
        back: "Returns the length (number of items) of an object.",
        tags: ["programming", "python"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        front: "<a> tag in HTML",
        back: "Defines a hyperlink.",
        hint: "Attribute 'href' specifies the URL.",
        tags: ["webdev", "html"],
        bucket: 0,
    },
];